Mokku, witches come
out on nights like this.
You must never go outside.
A witch?
That's right.
On full moon nights like this...
...the witch who lives in Devil's
Forest comes out to kidnap children.
What does she do after kidnapping them?
She drinks their blood.
Their blood?
Yes.
That is why children must
not stay out late playing.
That's a lie. It's just a story grownups
made up to stop kids from going out.
It is not made up!
The witch in Devil's Forest is a vampire.
Come on now, Mokku, go to sleep.
I'm not sleepy.
You're a good boy, aren't you, Mokku?
Keep that up and Grandpa won't help you
if the vampire comes and carries you off.
How boring.
See? You're sleepy after all.
Boring, so boring. I wish school
didn't exist. I hate school!
Now, now, stop grumbling. Time for bed.
You need to sleep early
so you can go to school.
Otherwise, the witch will come kidnap you!
I'm a puppet! Why would she ever kidnap me?
That's right.
Grandpa just can't help treating you like
a real human child.
Good night.
I want to become a real human, too.
Good morning!
Good morning, Mokku!
Did you do your homework?
Oh no, I forgot!
You'll be made to stand
in the hallway again!
Ah... Me too...
I hate math, too!
Me too. Mama said a witch would
come out last night, so I was terrified...
Me too! I was so scared!
Scaredy-cats. Witches aren't real.
I watched the street all night.
The only person who passed
by was the old lady Koshiki.
But Grandpa said so.
He said witches live in Devil's Forest...
...and vampires, too.
That's just superstition.
I bet you were shivering in bed.
Oh Dear God.
I don't believe in witches either.
I just thought if I told the teacher that,
he'd forgive me for the homework.
Then let's go explore
Devil's Forest right now.
If we go to school, they'll just make
us stand in the hallway anyway.
But...
Mokku's just scared of the witch after all.
Mokku is a chicken!
I promised Grandpa I'd
go straight to school!
Fine! We're not playing with
a coward like you anymore!
Let's go!
Yeah!
I'll coming too!
Mokku, don't go!
Shut up!
Real courage means going to school!
Mind your own business! I'm not a coward!
If you go to Devil's Forest,
you'll regret it!
Out of my way!
He's completely hopeless...
I misjudged you, Mokku.
There's no way witches exist.
Besides, I'm not scared at all!
The foot of that mountain
is Devil's Forest.
I'm starting to get scared.
If there's a witch, I'll catch her.
We'll make a fortune
putting her on display.
We'll be top-rate showmen.
We'll take the whole world by storm!
Rosanna, what do you want to do?
I don't want to go.
Right. We've never come
this far from home before.
Mokku, let's go back.
We came all this way!
Suit yourself. But I said no girls allowed!
Let's go.
Yeah.
Come on, Mokku. Let's go home.
Everyone is worried.
I'm a boy. I'm not going to be a coward.
What's the matter, Mokku?
If you're scared, go home with the girls.
Wait! I'm coming! Hey!
Lino, you go in first.
Marco, you go first.
N-No way. Franco's supposed to be first!
Look at you shivering.
You're shaking too, Franco!
I'm just trembling with excitement!
I'll go.
No child who ever entered that
cursed forest has survived.
May God protect them.
All right, move out once you're ready!
Wait!
What is it?
What are you doing here?
Please, take me with you.
An old fool like you
would only slow us down.
Mokku is my beloved grandchild. Please!
I said no, and that's final.
All right, let's go, everyone.
Take this with you.
Hold the cross high, and thrust it
toward the vampire if she appears!
Dear God, please protect Mokku.
Franco!
Lino!
Wait!
So close!
Franco!
Franco! Franco!
Help me!
Damn it!
Franco!
You're safe now. Papa is here.
Papa... Papa, I'm sorry.
What happened to Mokku?
Lino!
Marco!
What did you come here for?
A-Are y-you a w-w-witch?
Quite a feisty one, aren't you?
As if there would be
witches in these woods!
Mokku is my only reason for
living. Dear God, please save him.
Old man!
Where's Mokku? What
about Mokku? Is he safe?
No! That can't be! It can't be!
Both Lino and Marco were
eaten alive by wolves.
My boy was the only one who
managed to survive, but...
It was my fault... "Study, study"...
Forcing Mokku when he hated studying
so much... Mokku, please forgive me...
Be naughty, be lazy,
be selfish, it doesn't matter!
Mokku, please just come back to me!
Really? No school or church, and we
can just play from morning till night?
That's right. This is a
paradise for lazybones.
I love the sound of that!
Climbing trees, catching
birds... I hate studying!
Is that so?
I'm so glad I met you, old woman.
Is that so, is that so?
Mokku is a good boy.
Look over there, see?
Wow, a castle! Can I really live there?
It's pretty, but why are
there only red flowers?
Countess Leonard loves the color of blood.
Hello there! I'm Mokku. What's your name?
These little people can't speak at all.
Come along now.
Incredible!
Countess Leonard...
I have returned.
Good work. What is it?
She looks like the Oak Tree Fairy.
The Oak Tree Fairy?
Yeah, she's like a mother to me, but...
The Countess is much prettier.
Oh, thank you.
Then I shall be your mother from now on.
Really? I'd love that!
Of course. I adore children, after all.
The other children were wearing
crosses, but the wolves...
Poor things...
Do you mean Franco and the others?
No, just some foolish children.
I'm not foolish!
I know. Come along. Let us go to my room.
He was my husband,
and the lord of this castle.
He's dressed funny.
Yes, he passed away a very long time ago.
My family died out 500 years ago.
500 years ago? Then how
old are you, Countess?
I am 521 years old.
What?!
521 years old?!
I'm the prince of the castle!
I'm a prince! A prince!
Honestly, that Mokku is
completely hopeless.
Grandfather hasn't eaten a thing all
day and has been worrying sick...
He's not a human child.
You are not a human child.
Go sleep with the little people.
Hey, let's play, everyone!
Why are you working so hard?
We're allowed to play from
morning till night here, right?
Oh, I see. You can't speak.
Look, heave-ho!
See? Isn't it fun?
You guys try it too! Come on!
Come on!
Something's strange...
Just when I thought I could finally
suck the blood of a healthy child...
There isn't a single drop of
blood in his body, only water.
I have a good idea.
Mokku!
Yes!
What is it, Mama?
Don't you want some friends?
Yes, I want to be friends
with the little people, too.
The little people won't do.
None of them can speak.
So bring children from the village.
Yes, a cute girl would be nice.
You must have a girlfriend or two.
I sure do! Let's see... Anna, Rosanna,
and Sophia? I'm surprisingly popular.
Bring them all here. And make
sure they take off their crosses.
Why?
You hate school and church
too, don't you, Mokku?
Mama hates kids who go to church, too.
Yeah! I'm on my way!
Good. Make sure you bring them.
Mokku, now wherever you go,
you will obey my every command.
Now, go!
Bewitched and completely
hollowed out inside...
...Mokku obeyed the vampire's
orders and lured his girlfriends
to the castle in th forest.
At last, the long-awaited blood of
healthy children is hers to drink.
The vampire...
...finally reveals her
terrifying true form and...
...prepares to attack the young girls.
What will become of Mokku and his friends?
Look forward to next week's
Kashi no Ki Mokku.